ILYA KHOROBRYKH

FRONTEND DEVELOPER













8-999-457-44-97



horobryh17@gmail.com



Omsk, Russia



Portfolio

ABOUT ME

Hi there! I'm frontend developer with experience in building singlepage applications, based on React.js, Redux.js with Typescript. I focus on code quality, following trends, learning new technologies and improving my hard skills and English. I open for full-time/part-time remote or hybrid work and new frameworks (Angular, Vue).

SKILLS

- Javascript / Typescript
- React / React Native / Redux
- HTML5 / CSS3 / SCSS / SASS
- Rest API / Axios / Postman
- Unit tests / Storybook
- Material UI
- Git
- ESLint / Prettier
- Webpack

WORK EXPERIENCE

PERSONAL BLOG August 2022 - September 2022

Personal project on React/Redux-toolkit and Typescript. With using mongoDB, Express, JWT, React-markdown, Rest API

Libraries: SCSS, React-markdown, Material UI, ESLint, Axios

FLASHCARDS July 2022 - September 2022

Commercial project on React/Redux and Typescript. Using react hooks, redux-thunks, Postman requests tests and unit-tests.

Libraries: Redux-Thunk, React-router-dom, Formik, Axios, ESLint, Prettier, Husky, Material UI

TODOLIST February 2022 - June 2022

Personal project on React/Redux-toolkit and Typescript. With using react hooks, unit tests, snapshot testing, routing, working with Rest API, Postman requests tests and login/logout flow

Libraries: MUI, Redux-Thunk, Redux-toolkit, React-router-dom, React-hook-form, Axios, Storybook

EDUCATION

IT-INCUBATOR

Frontend developer 2021-2022

SIBERIAN STATE AUTOMOBILE AND HIGHWAY UNIVERSITY

Engineer (undergraduate, magistracy) 2012 - 2018

LANGUAGES

ENGLISH: A2/B1 (IN PROGRESS)

RUSSIAN: NATIVE